duematernity.com 2010-12-23

# Privacy Policy | About Us

---|---  
   
| |   
|  |   
| |   
| | | | |   
---  
Privacy Policy

## Due Privacy Policy & Secure Ordering

We at www.duematernity.com are especially sensitive to the privacy and security of our customers' information. 

We realize that you don't like spam and we don't like it either. From time to time we may send you special offers and freebies from DueMaternity.com or our parent company BlueHighway Inc., however you are welcome to opt out and will be removed permanently if you choose to do so. 

We use the latest SSL encryption technology to secure your order and personal information. We are hosted by Yahoo Stores and therefore offer the most advanced security precautions for ordering online. Credit card information is only transmitted securely to our secure servers and is not stored on our servers. 

* * *

## Partner Privacy Policies

Some information collected at Due Maternity, including email addresses, may   
Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com). 

* * *

## Yahoo! Privacy

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.   
   
| |   
| 

Welcome to Due Maternity, since 2002 we’ve been fashioning new moms in affordable designer maternity clothes. Due Maternity is an online maternity clothing shop that knows just because your shape has changed doesn't mean your style has. Since 2003 Due Maternity has helped expecting moms buy designer maternity clothes that are both stylish and comfortable. In 2005 Due began to design their own line of affordable fun, flirty pieces to accentuate the feminine figure while giving comfort that you need. Once you see their maternity clothing you'll think twice about raiding your partner's closet for oversized sweatpants and t-shirts. Due Maternity is all about making pregnant women even more beautiful. The full line of designer maternity clothes and accessories includes everything you'll need for the next nine months and beyond. From professional attire to formal wear and swimsuits, Due Maternity boutiques are where fashion-forward women can express themselves. A personal shopper will help you through the buying process, making your shopping experience easier and hassle-free. Shopping for maternity clothes online has never been easier, but if you have any sizing questions, or just want to place a phone order please call 1-866-SHOP-DUE for personal shopping advice

|   
| | Company Information  
Home  
Company Info  
Affiliate Program  
Store Locations  
Site Map  
Purchase Gift Certificates  
Product Index  
[Sites We Like](http://blog.duematernity.com/index.php/sites-we-like/)| Privacy & Security  
Privacy Policy  
FAQs & Sizing Info  
Gift Certificates  
Purchase Gift Certificates  
Product Index| Contact Information  

Returns & Shipping  
Resources  
FAQs & Sizing Info  
Store Locator

| Maternity Clothes You'll Love  
Due announces our first line of stylish maternity clothes - Due Designs Our new maternity dresses are arriving daily check [New Arrivals](http://www.duematernity.com/newarrivals.html/)  
If you need a look consult our stylist Due Stylist

| Recent Winners Page  
Enter to WIN our weekly maternity prize [ ENTER TODAY](http://www.duematernity.com/maternity-contest)[Atlanta Maternity Clothes](http://atlanta.duematernity.com/)  
---|---|---|---|---
